Night of the Living Carrots is a animation, comedy,
family film directed by Robert Porter.
After a mutant peculiar pumpkin blows up on the Murphy’s carrot lawn, zombie green beans begin
fighting the immediate place, and it’s up to the Creatures to preserve the evening again.
B.O.B. (voice), played by Seth Rogen.
General W.R. Monger (voice), played by Kiefer Sutherland.
The Missing Link (voice), played by David Kaye.
Wendy Murphy (voice), played by Julie White.
Carl Murphy (voice), played by Jeffrey Tambor.
Dr. Cockroach (voice), played by James Horan.
Night of the Living Carrots (also known as Monsters vs.
Aliens: Night of the Living Carrots) is a 2011 American animated short film
produced by DreamWorks Animation and based on the film Monsters vs.
A sequel to the 2009 short, Monsters vs.
Aliens: Mutant Pumpkins from Outer Space, the short follows the monster team (minus Ginormica
and Insectosaurus) taking on a mutated carrot army that can mind control others.
Cockroach determines that the only way to defeat them
and free their victims is for B.O.B.
to eat all of the carrots, which ultimately stops the invasion.
The short originally premiered in two parts exclusively on the Nintendo Video video service for the
Nintendo 3DS system; the first was released on October 13, 2011, and the second five days later.
It eventually received a general release on August 28, 2012, as part of the
Shrek's Thrilling Tales DVD and DreamWorks Spooky Stories Blu-ray.
The tone is lighthearted.